JOE：Hello, sit anywhere you like.
JOE：어서오세요. 아무데나 앉으세요~
Young Man：Do you have saké?
소년：혹시 사케도 있습니까?
JOE：Yep, wait one sec.
JOE：네~ 잠시만요.
JOE：Do you want it heated?
JOE：데워드릴까요?
Young Man：No.
소년：괜찮습니다.
JOE：Never seen you before. Are you from the east? Node 03?
JOE：한 번도 본적이 없는데... 동양인? Node 03에서 오셨나요?
Young Man：Yes. Is it rare to see one around these places?
소년：네. 여기선 마주치기 힘들죠?
JOE：Nah, where do you think this is? It's 08, any type of people can be found here.
JOE：그럴리가~ 이곳은 Node 08! 별의 별 사람들이 다 모여있죠.
JOE：But cold saké... indeed not an order you see every day.
JOE：물론 차가운 사케를 주문하는 사람은 거의 없었지만 말이죠.
Young Man：Back home we call this "Yukihie", refreshes the brain quite well... *Gulp!*
소년：우리 고향에선 「유키히에」라고 부른답니다. 머리가 아주 맑아지죠.... *꿀꺽*
JOE："Yukihie", I see...
JOE：「유키히에」라……
Young Man：*Gulp!*
소년：*꿀꺽*
JOE：Jasus, slow down. If you get drunk so fast, I'm gonna be the one carrying your limp body outside.
JOE：저기, 손님! 너무 빨리 마시는 것 같은데? 여기서 완전히 취해버리면 제가 또 부축해야 한다고요!
JOE：I've always had a fond interest in chatting with customers from other Nodes.
JOE：얘기도 좀 나누면서 좀 천천히, 오케이? 전 다른 Node 출신 손님이랑 얘길 나누는 것을 굉장히 좋아하거든요
Young Man：I'm... not exactly the type who's good at chatting.
소년：전…… 그렇게 얘기를 잘 하는 사람이 아닙니다만.
JOE：Haha, it's fine.
JOE：하하하! 괜찮아요!
JOE：I'm JOE, and you are?
JOE：내 이름은 JOE. 당신은?
Young Man：Hayato... *Gulp!*
소년：Hayato……*꿀꺽*
JOE：Did you get dumped?
JOE：실연이라도 당했나봐요?
Hayato：……... Why did you ask?
Hayato：……왜 그렇게 묻는 거죠?
JOE：Well, a young fella with a depressed look visiting an unfamiliar bar with the sole purpose of getting trashed.
JOE：우울한 표정을 한 젊은 사람이 새벽에 혼자 한 번도 가본 적이 없는 술집에 들어가 술을 들이 붓는다!
JOE：Pretty sure that means it has something to do with relationship issues... I think?
JOE：그럼 딱 80% 이상은 내가 추측한 것이 맞다....고 생각이 드는데?
Hayato：I'm... looking for a female.
Hayato：어떤 여자를…… 찾고 있어요.
JOE：Girlfriend?
JOE：여자친구?
Hayato：More or less my childhood friend, been missing for years already... *Gulp!*
Hayato：소꿉친구죠. 이미 실종된지 몇년이나 지났지만......*꿀꺽*
JOE：For years... could it be that she already... ah, I'm sorry.
JOE：몇년이라……그럼 이미……아, 죄송합니다.
Hayato：No need to be...I gave up a long time ago too.
Hayato：아니요…… 사실 저도 일찍이 포기했어요.
Hayato：In Node 03, missing people usually stay missing forever. It's practically a part of everyday life.
Hayato：저희 둘다 Node 03 출신이었으니. 그곳에선 사람이 실종되고 행방이 묘연해지는 일은 일상 다반사였죠.
Hayato：However, for some unknown reason, I just always have this feeling that she is right here in Node 08. A very powerful feeling too...*Gulp!*
Hayato：이유는 모르겠지만 계속 그녀가 Node 08에 있을 거라는 예감이 강하게 들어서.....*꿀꺽*
JOE：... If you're looking for someone, maybe you've come to the right location.
JOE：……사람을 찾는 거라면, 아마 장소를 제대로 짚으신 것 같군.
JOE：Not to brag about it, but this little shop really has all kinds of people visiting every day.
JOE：과장이 아니라, 이 곳엔 별의 별 사람들이 다 모인다고 했죠?
JOE：Give me some hints, maybe I can help. If you have a photo, even better.
JOE：아마 조금이라도 단서를 준다면, 아마 제가 도울 수 있을 지도 몰라요. 사진 같은 게 있으면 더욱 수월할 테고!
Hayato：A photo... I always have it with me. Here.
Hayato：사진……항상 몸에 지니고 다니죠. 자, 여기.
JOE：Hoho, lemme take a look. Heard from folks that Node 03 is where all the cute gals are at...
JOE：오오! 어디 한 번! 듣기론 Node 03에 미인이 그렇게 많다던데....
JOE：……！
JOE：……！
JOE：...... This person......
JOE：……이 사람은……